<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Intensity settings">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet helps you to open an image with fable imageviewer, and shows you how to use the intensity settings with the file.
If you have just completed the previous cheat sheet,
please close all your data file parts.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Data Browsing Perspective">
      <description>
         Please choose the data browsing perspective if you do not already have it selected (nothing will happen if you do not).
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.edna.workbench.application.perspective.DataPerspective)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Open File">
      <description>
         Right click on an example file from the &apos;data&apos; project containing a test image, then select &apos;Open With&apos;, then &apos;Fable Image&apos;.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select &apos;Autointensity&apos; tool">
      <description>
         Try clicking on the button labelled &apos;Scale the palette between the minimum and maximum intensity in the data&apos; from the toolbar above the plot, to turn autointensity on and off.
This button may be obscured on Linux if the window containing the plot is too small.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Turn off autointensity">
      <description>
         Ensure that autointensity is turned off by clicking on the button labelled &apos;Scale the palette between the minimum and maximum intensity in the data&apos; from the toolbar above the plot.
When autointensity is of, the &apos;Current&apos; intensity values (Min, Max) can be changed below the plot either by moving the slider, or typing in value.
Set the Max Intensity to maximum by moving the slider to the right.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Turn on autointensity">
      <description>
         Turn on autointensity by clicking on the button labelled &apos;Scale the palette between the minimum and maximum intensity in the data&apos; from the toolbar above the plot.
When autointensity is on, the &apos;Current&apos; intensity values can not be changed below the plot.
The Max Intensity is now automatically set to a lower value, instead of maximum value set in previous step.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
